{
    "id": "fa799858a42846db97b8b72540c1d0ce",
    "title": "Articles Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The world is ……………………… happy place.",
            "description": "A can mean one.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0c7c76a5f3444b8b9622326c1bba8003"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………….. accomplished dancer.",
            "description": "A/an can mean one.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ebb9ce80e36b4b8ead57ca0ca343582d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where is ………………………… hat that I brought from London?",
            "description": "We use the here because we are talking about a specific hat.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "f5654a9965114c64b08bcb91f9a20911"
        },
        {
            "question": "Aluminum is …………………………. useful metal.",
            "description": "We use a before a consonant sound. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "1a5634af74544881ab7e29fb33ea14bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Would you open …………………………. window, please?",
            "description": "We use the here because we are talking about a particular window.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "7a18f837824d476882e91221e4183e79"
        },
        {
            "question": "He returned after ………………………….. hour.",
            "description": "We use an before vowel sounds. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "891785c0cf444f859550b9ac54ea53cb"
        },
        {
            "question": "This is ………………………. answer to ……………………… problem that our teacher gave us.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "the, a",
                "a, a",
                "the, the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "8df231c4b6014675a6488623275ca94a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Which is …………………………. longest river in the world?",
            "description": "We use the before superlatives.",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "b1352be81b614414a0c3cdaf30dd04ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is ……………………….. close friend of mine.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "an",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e396ec79fe524bceb7b65499749e69b9"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to ………………………. school to see ……………………… principal.",
            "description": "Here we are talking about a particular school and the principal there. Hence, we use the.",
            "answers": [
                "the, the",
                "the, a",
                "a, a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "231f11e076d842efb21deee6d8f36368"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ……………………… dancer married to ……………………….. singer.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "a, a",
                "the, then",
                "a, the"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8b6c2897a731439c9949f702f3fdfeb8"
        },
        {
            "question": "December is ………………………….. coldest month.",
            "description": "We use the superlatives. ",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a",
                "an"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ed331997121d4aec9bde364d8ce54ef8"
        }
    ]
}